<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>pytest blog</title><link>/</link><description></description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><item><title>Blog 1.0</title><link>/2016/welcome-to-the-official-pytest-blog/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the launch of the official pytest blog!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pytest has grown from strength to strength over the past few years, and it's overdue that we have an official blog for releases and other project announcements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is now a &lt;a href="http://planet.pytest.org/"&gt;pytest planet&lt;/a&gt;, which is a blog aggregator. If you have your own blog and can tag some entries as 'pytest', we invite you to &lt;a href="https://github.com/fschulze/planet.pytest.org/blob/master/feeds.cfg"&gt;add your RSS feed there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is also the &lt;a href="http://hackebrot.github.io/pytest-tricks/"&gt;pytest tricks&lt;/a&gt; blog, so if you have a small demonstration of how to use a cool pytest feature, that might be the place for it. If you don't have your own blog, you can submit a guest post to either pytest-tricks or the main pytest blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It might be obvious that we're not the most gifted web designers, so we definitely welcome improvements at &lt;a href="https://github.com/pytest-dev/blog.pytest.org"&gt;the Github repository&lt;/a&gt;. This blog was first talked about at EuroPython 2015, so 11 months later, we thought it was more important to get it out there than to perfect the theme. Thanks to Javier Gonel and Andreas Pelme for their work to get it started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In upcoming months there are lots of things happening, with wrapping up the pytest development sprint and preparing for pytest 3.0. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">pfctdayelise</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">tag:,2016-06-24:2016/welcome-to-the-official-pytest-blog/</guid><category>meta</category><category>sprint2016</category></item><item><title>We have a blog</title><link>/2015/we-have-a-blog/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;And we have a blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a nice hacking day! A photo from the EuroPython 2015 sprints in Bilbao.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="We're legion" class="img-rounded" src="/2015/we-have-a-blog/images/legion.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">pelme</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">tag:,2015-07-25:2015/we-have-a-blog/</guid><category>meta</category><category>europython</category></item></channel></rss>